i woke up this morning with the
intention
of making a very specific video because
today is the anniversary
of the very first idea cafe that we i
happen to schedule on 9 11 and so we
changed the question last minute to
where were you 18 years ago
i already did that video and it's
uploaded to the idea cafe channel but
when i tried to do the same video for
this channel
it got it cut off because my ipad filled
up and then i tried to do it again
it i didn't realize anyway same problem
then the day transpired so i'm very glad
it didn't happen in the beginning one of
the other things i had scheduled for
today
was wednesday one of my very best
friends got in contact with me we hadn't
been in contact for a while you know how
are you doing
and so we scheduled a video conversation
for today at 10 a.m this morning when i
went to go do the videos like wait a
minute today's 9 11. isn't that our
anniversary
and so i was like hey what year is this
that we end up eating it's on our 11th
anniversary so that's kind of cool our
11th anniversary on 9 11 we ended up
scheduling a
group conversation video chat that so we
had that conversation before that
one of i got a text from what my kids
moms my kids best friend's mom from
cohousing they had chatted yesterday
online
and like hey when we could have a
playdate i was like we'll talk about
that because it's back to school time
her kids in a different school they're
going back to school we're not going
back to school
turns out they weren't able to go back
to school today so
they haven't been back to school yet so
it's the last time we could have a
playdate how perfect that we were able
to get together today
i was like well i have a conversation
from 10 that will probably go till noon
and then i have to get a tech board
meeting
so she was coming to pick up my child
and take her to the local park
they came while i was on the
conversation with with my friends but
they're always a little bit late
and she ended up coming so i kept
getting these dings on my phone i kept
checking it was this other person which
is its own its own thing
um which so this thing transpired
because i was having a conversation with
my friend on our anniversary and this
other play date was happening
the last time i hung out with those
friends the only time i've hung out with
those friends during coped
was when we all went to the beach
together about a month ago that was
because we got heat stroke we ended up
having to cancel the play date that
whole day transpired
that night when i went for a walk
because of the canceled play date i
ended up texting
one of the women who who was at that
play date
at the beach who had included me and
she's done that on several other
occasions
and i've done a video on on this exact
thing
and so i just texted her on my walk and
said thank you like you've done this
several times
and it wasn't anything huge and
impactful but it was i just wanted her
to know that i was grateful for that
today happens to be her birthday
she's also the mom of the child who
shares the birthday
with the one of my best friends who gave
me the necklace that fell off in my hand
on
her son slash my best one of my best
friend's birthdays
the person who had me wear the
protection jewelry that fell off in my
hand
has his birthday on the anniversary of
the anger event that happened a big huge
event that happened i've also done a
video on
in um at cohousing
today this guy texts me and
well i'm having a conversation with my
friend and
this transpired so he said what is this
so he said this is starting at 9 39 this
morning
you know you've the cr okay so i
actually have to start yesterday
so he just asked uh no school question
mark question mark no my kid won't be
attending school this year yeah i was
wondering
where you stood on school that was a few
weeks ago then he asked
on thursday you happy about school he
knows i'm not sending my kid to school
but anyway
it is what it is we are doing a bit at
the kitchen table throughout the day he
said yeah you not happy
how's your youtube channel i said
oh no he then you he's still staying you
know you've the creator has given you
that third eye for a reason and she gave
you that child too for a reason it's not
to be thrown away
i stated because i was about to be on a
conversation but i was like that's weird
so i just stated
not sure what you are saying i am
listening to my calling and taking care
of my child
he said i'm curious what's your calling
youtube videos question mark question
mark he shows up every few months to
question my
i don't know intention and like what i'm
doing in the world like i'm doing enough
i'm good i feel good about what i'm
doing anyway
so he's like the youtube where did this
go sorry i switched my phone
i said it i suck at it if it is my
colleen lol he said good i said no my
calling is dismantling capitalism and
creating a world that works for everyone
he said good you have something use it
now while you can i said i will
i am then 10 o'clock hit so i got in my
conversation at 1007 he sent me yeah
because we need you desperately this air
for from fires it's human cause
you are ahead of most this ten minutes
later you are a head of most you have
something good
i've been silently watching you work
most of those people are sheep
see what you've got to understand here
is the world will listen to you
not me my job is to keep pushing you in
no way do i need that
that's not your job but sure um
then but again i'm i was looking at this
because i'm waiting for my friend to
come but i wasn't reading them
then at 10 51 it's now been less than an
hour since he sent the one i didn't
respond to he said
talking about achieves nothing hey what
you what what you think
see i'm angry today and i want to blame
your culture your culture has done a lot
of bad
it's in my culture but whatever uh you
know i'm trying to have a chat with you
and all you can do is ignore us
who's up like really like whatever wtf
maybe you are not so different maybe you
were racist like everyone else
i thought you respected us and then it
says this person is unavailable on
messenger
so he has blocked me i can't find him i
can't respond hey i was busy for an
hour having a conversation i'm not
beholden to my comfort but this happened
today for a reason
he is intimately tied to the whole
journey that he told me that that it was
his birthday on the
anger anniversary that he blocked me
today on 9 11.
i'm like i don't know but this stuff is
so
amazing because if i hadn't met my
friend 11 years ago on 9 11 if we had
met on
september 20th i wouldn't remember right
she wouldn't remember we wouldn't
remember it was september 11 so we
wouldn't remember that it was our
anniversary we wouldn't know it was cool
we set up a call
if i wasn't if we didn't have facebook
if i hadn't remembered it like
our this play date from before then it
wouldn't matter that it's this friend
this other friend's birthday it happens
to be on 9 11. i love it cause we've
been friends for like
nine years and i feel like every year
i'm shocked that 9 11 is her birthday
and she's a twin so it's like both of
their birthdays
but i have another friend who's 9 11.
and i always remember she's 9 11.
so it's funny that i never remember i
have these friends every year like
there's a few that are born on my mom's
birthday i'm like oh you're my mom's
birthday i now remember who they are
actually the woman who came to the idea
cafe a year ago shares my mother's
birthday
and one of my very good friends oh that
this i'm gonna map this out because this
like anger event
my friend's birthday this birthday this
family co-housing all of it is like so
interconnected and i'm only aware of it
because it happens on these big days
and there's so much of this stuff that
occurs all of the time
that you i you won't even be aware about
i wouldn't be have been aware with the
anniversary that anchor event was
if i hadn't been keeping a journal for
my kid and then seeing that it was these
other two people's birthday the
feelings coach and this person who who
talked about protection jewelry
and the fact that he blocked me today
after i didn't respond for an hour and
is like you're never disrespecting
us who's us how am i disrespecting a
bunch of people because i didn't respond
to your text
that i don't need i don't need somebody
in my life checking up on me i don't
need someone seeing if i've saved the
world because
i'm on the universe's course i don't
need someone else telling me to look
after mother earth
she's my mother too she tells me all day
every day that she's in her
she's hurting and in pain i feel it i
don't need someone else telling me
i'm connected to all of the grandmas i
don't need you to tell me what they're
saying
they're telling me i need to learn i
have to listen to them
learn to listen to them but that's a
different a
totally different category i'm here to
teach the world how to listen to their
own inner talk
so i just i don't want to be the person
to teach you that that was not the
mission if it was dismantled capitalism
create a world that works for everyone
turns out
it's about listening to your inner guide
following your own guide
and i'm figuring it out but like i get
it
what it looks like i'm like i'm saving
the world and i'm 200 subscribers
and so that there's arrogance in there
and people want to like keep me in check
but i don't need your in check
this isn't this isn't arrogance this is
an ego
this is i'm doing it i already know how
we do it and i'm i'm on my path i don't
need to okay it through anyone else
if you want somebody else to do
something
that's gonna be a lot of pain like his
whole your racist
thing no you were being prejudiced in
the moment you thought it meant
that i was being racist that i was being
disrespectful of him and his entire
culture because i didn't respond to him
within an
hour right less than an hour
that is being prejudiced so you're
reacting to the outside like like it's
always that and i know i do this
constantly all day every day i was like
how dare you not look after mother earth
right
where am i not where can i take [ __ ] if
i'm getting triggered by the racism on
the outside
what is the racism here that i'm dealing
with and in so doing i have grown
immensely
and i invite everyone else to do the
same grow where you feel you need to
grow she's going to teach you where to
grow
you don't need some outside forest
telling you those
mother earth the grandmothers the
aunties they will kick your ass
if you're not doing it right we don't
need an outside other human
alive being kicking our ass for us she's
doing it just fine on her own
but the fact this all transpired on 9 11
the fact that his birthday shares the
birthday of the anniversary event the
fact that he's wanted with the
protection jewelry
that shares the birthday with the woman
who i talked to about the the the play
date the fact that today is the day
after the cleanse which i had a lot of
energy on which what happened
when i re scheduled the playdate that
beautiful deuterium getting together
with my siblings happened because of
that walk
it's all just so interconnected today's
the day after a cleanse as well because
i'm doing it every month
it's not as big of an energy day as it
was then
but it's still an energy day it's still
all this cool stuff coming together
around an anniversary that also just has
a lot of energy for the world
because it's a big day because it brings
it's not just september 20th right you
can see that these things come together
i invite you to start looking at them in
your life start keeping a daily journal
these things are weird
they're so weird so weird all right
i don't know what else is coming out of
this day but i needed to share it with
you
thank you